mytemplatez.com 2016-11-19

# Privacy Policy

By using or accessing MyTemplatez templates, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Please be sure to check our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use regularly as they may change as new services are added; such changes will be effective immediately and without prior written notice.

## Information Gathered by MyTemplatez:

MyTemplatez collects personal information only with your permission at the time of registration. The information you provide will never be provided to anyone and cannot be accessed by anyone except our accounts and customer service teams.

TemplatesBox.com may collect information that is non-personally identifiable (information that does not identify you personally) as a result of your visit(s) to our site. This information includes your IP address, your Internet service provider and your browser.

## MyTemplatez Uses of Information:

The information we collect about you in the course of our relationship is used to provide our service to you. For example, as we endeavor to protect your identity, we may use your demographic information to create a database of user profiles, select advertisements based on your information and for marketing analysis. In addition, we look at technical information to diagnose problems with our systems and to enhance the services we provide to you. We may use your information to track user-generated content and users to the extent necessary to comply as a service provider with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act. We will use your email address, without further consent, for administrative communications such as notifying you of major updates, for customer service purposes, to address copyright infringement or defamation issues, or to contact you regarding any content that you have posted to or downloaded from MyTemplatez.

## When MyTemplatez Discloses Information:

MyTemplatez does not share your personally identifiable information, including any of your user profile data that you create, with other organizations for their marketing or promotional uses.

MyTemplatez may share personally identifiable information about our users with third parties, including: (a) with your consent or as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy; (b) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary pursuant to a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order; (c) where required by law; or (d) at our sole discretion, where we deem necessary to respond to claims, to protect the safety of any individual or the public, or to protect the rights or property of MyTemplatez or any third party. We may disclose personally identifiable information to affiliated companies, sub-contractors, other agents or businesses or persons to: provide web site hosting, maintenance, and security services; fulfill orders; conduct data analysis and create reports; offer certain functionality; and assist MyTemplatez in improving the service and creating new service features. We require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Notice, we authorize only a limited use of such information, and we require these parties to use reasonable confidentiality measures to keep your information secure. MyTemplatez may also disclose to third parties anonymous aggregated user information that is not personally identifiable.

## Changing or Deleting Your Information:

You have the ability and control to remove or alter your account-specific information, including any user profile data that you provide to MyTemplatez at any time. Access and control over most user-provided personal information on MyTemplatez is readily available through the edit function on your profile. As a user of MyTemplatez, you may modify or remove any of your profile information at any time by logging into your account. Information will be updated promptly. Removed information such as your password, geographical information connected to your user ID, and any documents that you have uploaded to MyTemplatez may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time, and thus may continue to be publicly available across features of MyTemplatez such as its search engine, but will not be generally accessible by MyTemplatez or users of MyTemplatez.

## Children Under 13:

**IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS MyTemplatez AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER.**

MyTemplatez complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on the MyTemplatez. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who has become a member of the MyTemplatez, then please contact MyTemplatez via contact form to have that child's account terminated and information deleted.

## In the Event of Merger or Sale:

In the event that MyTemplatez is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, or undergoes a change of control or any form of sale or transfer of some or all of its assets, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from users as part of that merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

## Contacting MyTemplatez:

Please contact MyTemplatez with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice using our contact form.
